<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Preeti Ravindra on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://cybersnacker.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Preeti Ravindra on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://cybersnacker.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>COMMUNITY</title>
      <link>https://cybersnacker.github.io/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cybersnacker.github.io/community/</guid>
      <description>This section contains my contributions in maintaining and fostering the security community by lending my security expertise
CONFERENCES 16th Executive Women&amp;rsquo;s Forum National Conference 2018: Served as steering committee member to identify relevant and important themes in information security, risk and privacy. I reviewed submissions in the AI track for this conference WiCyS Conference 2017: Served as program committee member to review and select conference submissions for WiCyS 2017 Conference LEADERSHIP I produced content for the NextExec Podcast Season 3 in the role of co-lead of Executive Women&amp;rsquo;s Forum&amp;rsquo;s podcast team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MEDIA</title>
      <link>https://cybersnacker.github.io/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cybersnacker.github.io/media/</guid>
      <description>This section features coverage of my work as well as my profile
PRESS Data Privacy Week - An interview style news article about data privacy challenges from a data science and security perspective and
PODCASTS Emerging Voice of Humans of InfoSec - I talk about my career journey in to doing AI for Cybersecurity Scuba Gear Required: A Deeper Dive into AI/ML/DL - Specific application and use cases of AI for security Keeping it Real About Artificial Intelligence - 101 for security practitioners TV/STREAMING Darkweb: Fighting Cybercrime - This documentary was produced by Discovery Channel and aired on the Science Channel featuring the technological advances in solving cybercrime </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RESEARCH</title>
      <link>https://cybersnacker.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cybersnacker.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>My research is at the intersection of security, data science and machine learning.
PATENTS Security Incident Disposition Predictions Based on cognitive evaluation of security knowledge graphs Inferring Temporal Relationships for Cybersecurity Events Exploit Kit Detection </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TALKS</title>
      <link>https://cybersnacker.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cybersnacker.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description>SECURITY EWF 2017: Anatomy of a Ransomware Attack DATA SCIENCE, ML, AI BSidesPGH 2022: Clippy or SkyNet for your SOC @ 7:19:40 Watson for Cybersecurity @ Kennesaw State University </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
